We have two more operators remaining: floor
division, and exponents. Floor division returns
an integer for a result without a remainder. On
line 18, I will reset the score to 300. Then, on
line 19, I will type score //=11. The slash slash
represents floor division. When I run this code,
the result does not show because ...and this
happens often, we still need a print statement,
which I will copy and paste... When I run this
code now, the result is 27, as 300 divided by 11
is 27 with a remainder of 3, but, again, with a
floor division operation, only the integer in the
result is preserved. The last operator to cover:
exponents. Whereas multiplication is done with one
asterisk, exponents are done with two asterisks. I
will add the code to raise score to the power of 2
on line 22 and then print the score on line 23.
When I rerun the code, the final result is 729,
which is 27 raised to the power of 2, or 27 times
27. One more item of note: if you have multiple
assignments in the same statement, the operators
are assessed from right to left. In the statement
“x = y = 2”, first 2 is assigned to y, and then y,
which is now 2, is assigned to x. Or if you have
y = 2 followed by x = y += 2, then you add 2 to
y, which becomes 4, and then 4 is assigned to x.